# Oleksandr Azhyntarev

Toronto, ON | sasha@gmail.com | +90 541 999 99 99 | linkedin.com/in/yourusername github.com/yourusername

## **Summary**

I offer approximately **3 years** of hands-on experience developing, designing, shipping large-scale products where availability, performance and security are paramount. I am an accelerated graduate with a Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering. I have established myself as a versatile software engineer who enthusiastically takes on new problems across the full-stack.

#### **Skills**

PHP, TypeScript, JavaScript, Python, Laravel, SQL, React, Django, AWS, DigitalOcean, Nginx, Git, UNIX

# Experience

### Software Engineer, Bella

Jun 2024 - Present

Company is engaged in production of food, exports to over 20 countries, including the USA, Australia, Spain and Turkey.

**Tech Stack:** PHP, Laravel, TypeScript, React, Node.js, Express.js, JavaScript, Pl/SQL, MySQL, EBS Oracle, HTML, CSS, Bash, Git, Linux.

#### Full-stack Web Developer, Shkolo

Oct 2022 - Jan 2024

Developing an online school diary, used in over 1500+ schools. Platform for conducting online private lessons with tutors with 900,000+ regular users.

- Integrated promo codes into applications, reducing the administrative workload by 10%.
- Implemented a bug reporting system, decreasing the support team's workload by 15%.
- Improved calendar functionality in the online lesson application, enhancing scheduling efficiency.
- Enhanced the online lesson application, improving calendar functionality for better scheduling.
- Developed a system to manage teacher activity on the platform, leading to a 10% increase in previously inactive teachers becoming active.

**Tech Stack:** PHP, Laravel, Typescript, JavaScript, React, Redux, MySQL, Next.js, Node.js HTML, CSS, Axios, DigitalOcean, Nginx, Bit Bucket, Bash, Git, Linux.

# Frontend Web Developer, PlanA

Jun 2022 – Sep 2022

Building inventory management applications for customers in retail.

- Enhanced the user interface for better customer experience, resulting in a 15%. increase in user satisfaction.
- Developed a real-time inventory tracking feature.
- Designed intuitive and responsive user interfaces, enhancing overall user engagement.

Tech Stack: TypeScript, JavaScript React, Ag-Grid, Axios, GraphQL, HTML, CSS, styled-components, Bit Bucket.

#### Backend Web Developer, Swimcloud

Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

Developing an application for recruiting athletes to universities in the USA.

- Processed competition results from LENEX files and added them to the database.
- Developed a pet project for a library book rental application.
- Fixed small bugs to improve application stability and performance.

Tech Stack: Python, Django, MySQL, Nginx, uWSGI, GitHub, Git, Linux, Bash.

#### Education

**Bachelor of Science**, Software Engineering 2019-2022 (Accelerated Individual Plan) | **Plovdiv University "Paisii Hilendarski"**, Plovdiv, Bulgaria